const adobeAnimateShortcuts_questions = [
  {
    question: "What is the shortcut for Selection?",
    answer: "V",
    category: "adobeAnimateShortcuts"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the shortcut for Sub-Selection?",
    answer: "A",
    category: "adobeAnimateShortcuts"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the shortcut for Free Transform?",
    answer: "Q",
    category: "adobeAnimateShortcuts"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the shortcut for 3D-Rotation?",
    answer: "Shift + W",
    category: "adobeAnimateShortcuts"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the shortcut for Lasso?",
    answer: "L",
    category: "adobeAnimateShortcuts"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the shortcut for Pen?",
    answer: "P",
    category: "adobeAnimateShortcuts"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the shortcut for Text?",
    answer: "T",
    category: "adobeAnimateShortcuts"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the shortcut for Line?",
    answer: "N",
    category: "adobeAnimateShortcuts"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the shortcut for Rectangle?",
    answer: "R",
    category: "adobeAnimateShortcuts"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the shortcut for Oval?",
    answer: "O",
    category: "adobeAnimateShortcuts"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the shortcut for PolyStar?",
    answer: "PolyStar",
    category: "adobeAnimateShortcuts"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the shortcut for Pencil?",
    answer: "Shift + Y",
    category: "adobeAnimateShortcuts"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the shortcut for Paint Brush?",
    answer: "Y",
    category: "adobeAnimateShortcuts"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the shortcut for Brush?",
    answer: "B",
    category: "adobeAnimateShortcuts"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the shortcut for Bone?",
    answer: "M",
    category: "adobeAnimateShortcuts"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the shortcut for Paint Bucket?",
    answer: "K",
    category: "adobeAnimateShortcuts"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the shortcut for Gradient Transform?",
    answer: "F",
    category: "adobeAnimateShortcuts"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the shortcut for 3D-Translation?",
    answer: "G",
    category: "adobeAnimateShortcuts"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the shortcut for Polygon?",
    answer: "L",
    category: "adobeAnimateShortcuts"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the shortcut for Add Anchor Point?",
    answer: "=+",
    category: "adobeAnimateShortcuts"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the shortcut for Rectangle Primitive?",
    answer: "R",
    category: "adobeAnimateShortcuts"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the shortcut for Oval Primitive?",
    answer: "O",
    category: "adobeAnimateShortcuts"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the shortcut for Bind?",
    answer: "M",
    category: "adobeAnimateShortcuts"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the shortcut for Magic Wand?",
    answer: "L",
    category: "adobeAnimateShortcuts"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the shortcut for Delete Anchor Point?",
    answer: "-_",
    category: "adobeAnimateShortcuts"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the shortcut for Convert Icon Point?",
    answer: "Shift + C",
    category: "adobeAnimateShortcuts"
  }
];

export default adobeAnimateShortcuts_questions;
